<ContractDocument xmlns="http://example.org/ContractMarkup"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://example.org/ContractMarkup ContractMarkup.xsd">
    <Block name="GeneralConditions">
        <Clause id="noGuaranteeOfWorkOrExclusivity">
            <Title>No guarantee of work or exclusivity</Title>
            The {{Contract Authority}} is not, by executing this {{MICTA}}:
            <SubClause>bound to issue any {{Order Proposal}} to the {{Supplier}};</SubClause>
            <SubClause>bound to engage the {{Supplier}} to supply any goods, services and/or other activities or to enter into any {{Contract}}; or</SubClause>
            <SubClause>restricted in any way from engaging any other person to supply any goods, services and/or other activities:
                <SubClause> of any type, including goods, services and/or other activities that are the same as or similar to any {{Supplier's Activities}} or {{ICT Activities}}; or</SubClause>
                <SubClause> at any location where, or in respect of any project that, the {{Supplier}} may be required to supply goods, services and/or other activities.</SubClause>
            </SubClause>
        </Clause>
        <Clause id="noRepresentation">
            <Title>No representation</Title>
            Clause {{noGuaranteeOfWorkOrExclusivity}} applies even though the {{Contract Authority}} may have provided the {{Supplier}} with a forecast or estimate of the goods, services, {{ICT Activities}} and/or other activities that the {{Contract Authority}} or any {{Eligible Customer}} may require at any time. The {{Supplier}} acknowledges that any forecasts or estimates do not constitute a representation of the goods, services and/or other activities the {{Contract Authority}} or any {{Eligible Customer}} may require in any period.
        </Clause>
        <Clause id="definitionsAndInterpretation">
            <Title>Definitions and interpretation</Title>
            <SubClause>
            In this MICTA capitalised terms have the same meaning as in the ICTA (unless they are assigned a different meaning below) and the following terms have the meaning assigned to them below:
                <Define term="Contract Authority" display="show">means the relevant authority or agency executing this agreement.</Define>
                <Define term="MICTA" display="show">means the master ICT agreement under which this agreement operates.</Define>
                <Define term="Supplier" display="show">means the entity providing goods, services and/or other activities under this agreement.</Define>
                <Define term="Order Proposal" display="show">means a document proposing specific goods, services and/or other activities for approval and execution under this {{MICTA}}.</Define>
                <Define term="Contract" display="show">means any contract formed under or related to this arrangement, including those executed through an {{Order Proposal}}.</Define>
                <Define term="Supplier's Activities" display="show">means the activities the {{Supplier}} undertakes under this agreement, including but not limited to the provision of goods or services.</Define>
                <Define term="ICT Activities" display="show">means any information, communications, and technology-related activities undertaken under this agreement.</Define>
                <Define term="Eligible Customer" display="show">means any customer eligible to place orders under this agreement in accordance with its terms.</Define>
            </SubClause>
        </Clause>
    </Block>
</ContractDocument>
